(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T14:06:14.548720",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ちっぽけな星よ
Dear little star,
まわりつづけて…
keep revolving...
あふれそうに輝いて
Shining so brightly,
流れてゆく
flowing away...
きれいなままで
Staying pure and beautiful,
歩き出す
I start to walk.
愛を連れて
Bringing love along,
奏でるように
as if playing a melody,
信じている
I keep on believing.
どんな形でも
No matter what form it takes,
太陽は昇るから きっと
the sun will rise for sure.
その胸の中には 何があるの
What is inside that heart of yours?
歩き出す
We'll start to walk,
愛になって
becoming love,
光の中へ
towards the light.
大丈夫
It'll be alright,
どんな未来でも
no matter what future awaits.
太陽は昇るから
The sun will rise,
きっと
for sure.
歩き出す
We'll start to walk,
愛になって
becoming love,
光の中へ
towards the light.
大丈夫
It'll be alright,
どんな未来でも
no matter what future awaits.
太陽は昇るから
The sun will rise,
きっと
for sure.
小さな 人の子よ
Oh, little human child...
森へ 迷い込んで
Who wandered into the forest...
ぼうや は
The boy...
大きな この羽 が
These large wings...
ぼうや は 見えない の ね
cannot be seen by the boy.
なにも 知らない
Knowing nothing at all,
まあるい ほっぺ よ
those round little cheeks.
ねむれや ねむれ
Sleep now, sleep.
水辺 に おいで
Come to the waterside.
ぼうや の 夢 は
Your dreams
竜 の 背 に 運ばれて
will be carried on a dragon's back,
山 の 向こう へ 消える
disappearing beyond the mountain.
夜更け の 心 も
Even the midnight heart
ならんで ねむる
sleeps side-by-side.
七つ 数えたら
When I count to seven,
仲良く ねむって く
they sleep happily together.
なにも 見えない
Seeing nothing at all,
小さな おめめ よ
those tiny little eyes.
ねむれや ねむれ
Sleep now, sleep.
そよぐ 草むら に おいで
Come to the swaying grass.
母さん を 探して は
Searching for mother,
空 の 向こう へ 帰る
returning beyond the sky.
竜 の 背 に 運ばれて
Carried on a dragon's back,
山 の 向こう へ 消える
disappearing beyond the mountain.
みなさんどうも！
Hello everyone!
ナレーションの雪花ラミィです。
I'm Yukihana Lamy, your narrator.
今日はせっかく3Dになれたということで、モーニングルーティンに挑戦してみたいと思います。
Since I finally made it into 3D today, I wanted to try doing a morning routine.
さあ、ここは今ちょうど起きたところですね。
Now, this is right after I just woke up.
寝ぞうは悪くないと思っているのですが、まあ大福に聞いてみないと真実はわからないですね。
I think my sleeping posture isn't bad, but I guess I'd have to ask Daifuku to know the truth.
やっと起き上がって、行動を始めました。
I finally got up and started moving around.
起きたらまずするのは、え、洗顔です。
The first thing I do when I wake up is, um, wash my face.
顔を洗うと目が覚めますし、すっきりして気持ちがいいですよね。
Washing your face wakes you up and feels so refreshing, right?
ばしゃばしゃ…
Splash, splash...
まず、よく洗っていきます。
First, I'll wash up nicely.
そしたらこの後に、歯磨きをします。
And then, after that, I'm going to brush my teeth.
歯も大切にしないといけないですからね。
You have to take good care of your teeth, after all.
しっかりと磨いていきます。
I'll make sure to brush them thoroughly.
ちなみにラミィは歯磨き粉をつけずに電動歯ブラシを使う派なんですが、皆さんはどうでしょうか？
By the way, I'm the type who uses an electric toothbrush without toothpaste, but what about you guys?
そして次はスキンケアです。
And next is skincare.
結構ね、丁寧にとしっかりします。
I take good, thorough care with it.
配信の時にもお顔は常に見られていますから、この辺は大事にしていきたいですね。
My face is always visible during streams, so I want to take good care of this area.
そして最後は、髪型を整えます。
And finally, I'll fix my hair.
このね、ハートのアホ毛、これはねトレードマークなのでしっかりと整えます。
This heart-shaped ahoge is my trademark, so I'll make sure it's neatly in place.
あと、ここで気合が入ります。
And here I get my fighting spirit ready.
これね、気合を入れるのも大切なことです。
Getting pumped up like this is also important.
よし。
Alright!
頑張るぞ、頑張るぞ。
Let's do our best, let's do our best!
そしたら次は朝食の準備をしていきたいと思います。
And next, I'd like to prepare breakfast.
基本的にあんまりしっかりとした朝食を撮るって言うのはないんだけれども、
I don't usually eat a very hearty breakfast, but...
ま、せっかくね、モーニングルーティーンを取るっていうことなので、今日はしっかりめに作って食べてみることにしました。
Since it's a morning routine video, I decided to make a hearty one and give it a try today.
そして朝食後は健康的にスムージーを飲んでみたりしました。
And after breakfast, I tried drinking a healthy smoothie.
ラミィね、あの、一時期スムージー作りにハマっていたことがあって、あの小松菜バナナとか、ほうれん草リンゴとか、っていうのがすごく好きです。
I used to be really into making smoothies for a while, and I love komatsuna banana, spinach apple, and things like that.
これミキサーですぐできるのですごく便利ですよね。
You can make them right away with a mixer, so it's super convenient.
そしてご飯を食べ終わったらお着替えをします。身だしなみもばっちり整えていきます。
And once I finish eating, I'll change clothes. I'll make sure my appearance is properly put together too.
そして朝活配信をします。
And then I do my morning stream.
これね、ちょっとちょこちょこ寝起きでやってしまったりとかもしています。
And sometimes I might do this a bit right after waking up.
で、ラミィ、実はあんまり朝起きるのが得意ではなくて、
And actually, I'm not really good at waking up early,
でも皆さんとなんかゆっくりお話しできるこの時間でいるのがすごく大好きなので、これからも続けていきたいなと思っています。
but I love spending this time chatting slowly with you all, so I hope to keep it going.
結構ね、ラミィ考える時目が上に行っちゃう癖とか話しながら体を揺らしちゃう癖があるんですけど、
And you know, when I think, my eyes tend to drift upwards, or I have a habit of swaying my body while talking,
3Dだとすごくよく分かりますね。
which is super noticeable in 3D.
そして最後はバイバイをして終わります。皆さんどんな朝を過ごされておりますでしょうか？
And finally, I'll say goodbye and wrap up. How are you all spending your mornings?
今日も元気に張り切ってまいりましょう。雪花ラミィでした。
Let's do our best and stay energetic today too. This was Yukihana Lamy!
ああっ。
Ah...
皆さん！皆さん！
Everyone! Everyone!
こんなみです！皆さんこんなみです！
Here's Lamy! Everyone, here's Lamy!
雪花ラミィです！
I'm Yukihana Lamy!
今日は皆さん雪花ラミィの3D配信にお越しいただきありがとうございます。
Thank you all so much for coming to Yukihana Lamy's 3D stream today.
ちょっと早速なんですがね、皆さん気になれと思うので、下から、下から見せて、
And um, right away, since I think you're all curious, let's show it from below, from below.
いこうかなと思います。
Let's take a look.
これはラミィの足
This is Lamy's legs,
からの、お胸。
and then, my chest.
こんな感じになっております。
This is how it looks.
もうすごい、緊張して、もう心臓の音が自分ですごい聞こえるぐらい緊張するんですけど、
I'm so nervous, my heart is beating so loud I can hear it myself,
今日ね、ちょっと皆さんとこう素晴らしい思い出を作っていけるように頑張りたいと思います。
but I want to do my best today to create wonderful memories with everyone.
そしてなんと今回大福も3D化しました！大福！
And what's more, this time Daifuku has also been made into 3D! Daifuku!
どう？どう？
How is he? How is he?
大福、おい、こちらでほら！みんなに、みんなに見てもらおう！ほら！
Hey Daifuku, look over here! Let's show everyone! Look!
あ、あ、あ、よれる。カメラマンさんよれますか？
Ah, ah, ah, he's swaying. Can the cameraman zoom in?
こんな感じ！ベイク、さっきねお膝の上にのってたんですけれども、こんな感じになっております。
Like this! Daifuku was sitting on my knee earlier, but this is how he looks.
はあ、緊張する。
Phew, I'm so nervous.
そしてこちらラミィのお部屋になっております。
And this is Lamy's room!
えーとじゃね、ちょっとこのこっちの、あれ、この大きな、ちょっと博物館をね、
And um, let's check out this big museum...
見てもらおうかなと思うんですが、
I mean, let's have everyone take a look at it,
そっちじゃないですね。
though that's not it.
こっち、じゃじゃじゃーん！見てください！これ、ラミィの一番好きな写真です。
And over here, ta-da! Look at this! This is Lamy's favorite photo.
そして、えーぐいっと来て、えこっちにはね、ごきげんのブルークラッパーの写真と、えそしてこちらですね、あのモーリーオンラインさんで
And coming around here, over here is the photo of the cheerful Blue Clapper, and also over here, the one from Molly Online...
コラボさせていただいた、ぐちこ先生が描いてくださった
Drawn by Guchico-sensei, who we collaborated with—
え、ごきげんのイラストも飾っております。
um, we're also displaying Gokigen illustrations.
うん、うん、うん。いいですね。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's nice.
とか。
And stuff.
あとね、こっち側に。
And, you know, on this side.
えとね、こっちだ。
Um, right here.
ここだ。
Right here.
こち、こっちだ。そこだ。
H-Here, here. Right there.
ここ、ここにね、え、サインを飾ったりとかもしています。
Here, um, we also display signatures and things.
것도そう。
This is also...
集合。
Everyone together.
いつかね、ここに、あの、ごきげんもね、
Someday, um, here, like, Gokigen too...
混ざれたらいいなと思っております。
I hope we can all be mixed in together.
みたいな感じです。
Something like that.
どう、どうでしょう。
How, how is it?
あ、あとね、そう、皆さんちょっとね、見たことないと思うので、
Oh, and also, you guys probably haven't seen this,
じゃーん。
Ta-da!
どうですか？
How is it?
これね、そう、いつもこの2Dなので、
This, you see, I'm normally in 2D,
この後ろ姿が見えないと思うんですけれど、
so you probably can't see this back view, but
こんなふうになっております。
this is how it looks.
あのね、さっき、あのコメント見てたら、こういうこの髪、髪飾りがすごい綺麗ってコメントがね、
You know, earlier, when I was reading the comments, someone said this hair ornament is so pretty,
あります。実はね、こんな、こんなふうになってます。
and you know what? Actually, it's made like this.
このね、キラキラが、あの、結構ね、どういうふうにつけてるんだろうって今までね疑問に思ってた方いると思うんですけど、
This sparkly bit—I think some of you have probably wondered how it's attached until now, but
実はね、この後ろにこんなふうに付いてます。
actually, it's attached to the back like this.
はあ。
Whew.
いや、すごい緊張して。
Man, I'm so nervous.
緊張してなんかちょっとはあはあしてるの聞こえてないかな、大丈夫かな。
I'm so nervous, I wonder if you can hear me panting a bit, is it okay?
すごい、すごい息が楽なってしまう。申し訳ない。
Wow, my breathing gets so short. I'm sorry.
じゃあ、こんな感じになっております。
Well, it's looking like this.
どう？
How?
あんまりあとね、さっきコメント見てたら、ラミーの動きが、
Also, earlier when I looked at the comments, it said Lamy's movements...
想像できないって、あの、書いてあったんですけど、どうでしょう。
are unimaginable, they wrote, so how is it?
こんな感じです。
This is how it is.
最高に可愛い、ありがとう。
Super cute, thank you!
ありがとう。
Thank you!
あとどうですか、この部屋見てみたいところとかあれば、コメントで、あれば、
Also, how is it, if there's any place in this room you'd like to see, if you leave it in the comments...
ああ、酒瓶。
Ah, sake bottles.
あ、そうそうそうそうそう。
Ah, right right right right.
これ、これこれこれこれ。じゃーん。
This, this, this, this. Ta-da!
これは、あのね、譜面台です。
This is, um, a music stand.
いつも弾いてる譜面台、こんな感じになってます。
The music stand I always play on, it looks like this.
そう、譜面台はこの感じ。
Yes, the music stand is like this.
あとね、さっきね、そこコメントで、あと酒瓶？酒瓶、こっか。こっちに。
And, you know, earlier in the comments, sake bottles? Sake bottles, over here. Over here.
これだ。寄れるかな。
This. Can we zoom in?
これね、あの、日本酒です。
This, you see, is sake.
日本酒雪花。
Sake Yukihana.
これね、大事なものなので、いつでも飲めるように置いてあります。
This is important, so I placed it so I can drink it anytime.
え、という ことでね。
Uh, so...
さて、そんな私のラミーの素敵な3Dボディを
Now, to make my, Lamy's wonderful 3D body,
もっともっと輝かせるために、
shine even more brightly,
今日はですね、最高のプロデューサーたちをお呼びしました！
today, I've invited the best producers!
えー、それでは、呼びたいと思います。
Uh, well then, I'd like to call them out.
ラミーのプロデューサーさんたち、どうぞ！
Lamy's producers, please come on!
はーい！
Yay!
手を上げて clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands across the sea,
clap your hands 届くように
clap your hands so it reaches far,
手を叩こう 手を叩こう ほら一緒に everybody
let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands, c'mon together everybody!
ブブブン
Vroom vroom!
バイクで、バイクで来た
I came by bike, by bike!
かけつけてきた感出したかった
I wanted to give the vibe of rushing over.
なるほど
I see.
ありがとう、という事で
Thank you! With that said,
ごきげんの3人に今日は来ていただきましたー！
today we have the 3 Gokigen members here with us!
やったー！やったー！
Yay! Yay!
ええとですね、今からですね、みんなに制限時間3分使って、ラミーをプロデュースしてもらいます。
Uh, so, starting now, everyone will have a 3-minute time limit to produce Lamy.
はいはいはいはい。
Right, right, right.
やばっ。
Oh no.
今ちょっとよだれ出てた。大丈夫。好きね。好きからさ、なんかすごい、感情が薄まっちゃって、おいしくないんだよね。
I was drooling just now. It's fine. Lamy, you're too... Your emotions get so thin, it's not funny.
オマルン、オマルン今日なんか声小さいね。
Omarun, Omarun, your voice is kind of quiet today.
おっさんやんけ、やめろ。
You sound like an old man, stop it!
ちょっと、進行してください。
Please proceed with the show.
この3分間の間は、ラミィがみんなの言うことを聞きます。
For these next three minutes, Lamy will listen to everything everyone says.
え？本当ですか？
Eh? Really?
マジか、やだ！
Seriously? No way!
ここ全員おっさん！
Everyone here is an old man!
一応ね、あの使える小道具が、えっとお酒の瓶とかあとお酒のグラスみたいなものが使えますが、まあ使っても使わなくても大丈夫です。
You know, props you can use include sake bottles or sake glasses, but it's okay whether you use them or not.
お酒しかないのか。
Only alcohol, huh?
お酒じゃあ……
Alcohol, well...
ちょっとね、申し訳ない。
Sorry about that.
お酒しかない、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ、
Only alcohol, well, well, well, well...
ということで、順番はオマルン、シシロン、ネネちゃんの順番でチャレンジしていただきたいと思いますが、
So, the order will be Omaru-n, Shishiro-n, then Nene-chan, for the challenges,
オマルン、どうですか？いけますか？
Omaru-n, how about it? Can you do it?
いけます、いけます、いつでももうね、任せてくださいよ。
I can, I can, anytime, just leave it to me!
え、じゃあね、そういう、そんなオマルンのために、ために？そんなオマルンのチャレンジ、それでは、
Well then, for Omaru-n, for her challenge, ready,
よーい、スタート！
set, start!
頼むぞ、オマルン！え、やってくれ、色々。
Count on you, Omaru-n! Do various things!
したのまずごきげん消してもらえます？
First, could you wipe that cheerful mood off?
あ、待って、これわかる、わかる、でもわかる。ちょっとこれ、邪魔だよね。
Ah, wait, I get this, I get this, but I get it. It's kind of in the way.
スクショ、スクショ撮りてえのに、あの扇風機だからさっき言ってくれた。その酒瓶と、あの、おちょこかな？なんか、お酒のさ、ほら、これがラミィさんお酒の案件とかどうですか？
I want to take a screenshot, but because of the fan you mentioned earlier, that sake bottle and the small cup? Like, Lamy-san, what about a sake sponsorship or something?
あ、それは欲しいですね。
Ah, I'd want that.
あと、二合ぐらいの日本酒の、ボトルだけ。
Also, just a bottle of about 2-gou of sake.
ドン。
Boom.
はい。
Yes.
あ、あ、あ、そっか。
Ah, ah, ah, I see.
あ、こっちだ。
Ah, this way.
あ、待って、ちょっと、それ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょうどいいよ皆さん。
Ah, wait, wait, that's just right, everyone.
待って、私の手のひらに、すごいね。こう、こうに。
Wait, in the palm of my hand, amazing. Like this.
ちょっと待って、これもう、まいった、まいった。よーいしょ、よーいしょ、はい。
Wait, I give up, I give up. Heave-ho, heave-ho, yes.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
あ、まあ、そういう日もあるよね。
Ah, well, days like that happen, right?
あるね。まだ、まだ飲む時間じゃない。
Yeah. It's not drinking time yet.
ちょっと、あの、別の、別のシーンからお願いしてもいいですか？
Can I ask from a different scene?
じゃあ、え、ラミィさんのさ、ペタッて座れる、なんか、さ。
Then, um, Lamy-san's flat-seated pose, something like that.
あ、座れるよ？
Ah, you can sit?
なんか、あの、ペタんでわかる、ペタん、お姉さん座りの足広げたバージョンね。
Like, "petan", you know, "petan", the knee-sitting with legs spread version.
え、なんでそこになぜそれがくんの？
Eh, why did that come out there?
あ、足が、ん？見えるかな。
Ah, my legs, hmm? Can you see?
わあー！
Wow!
え、でもそんな感じ、え、もうちょっとだけさ、足広げられる？
Eh, but like that, eh, can you spread your legs just a little more?
え、どういうこと？
Eh, what do you mean?
こう？太もも？
Like this? Thighs?
はっ！
Ha!
やばい！
No good!
あ、いいですね、いいですね！
Ah, that's good, that's good!
まずいよ、どういうこと？
This is bad, what do you mean?
これを見、なんだろう、えー、あ、ちょっと！
Looking at this, I wonder, um, ah, wait!
あー！
Aah!
それにさ、上からさ、上からさ、あのさ、ラミィもさ、上を見る感じ。
Also, from above, from above, um, Lamy, looking upwards.
で、ちょっとあの、ポルカとの好感度少し上げて。
And, um, raise your favorability with Polka a little bit.
好感度を落ちもって。
Lower your favorability.
あらー！
Oh my!
ここで首をかしげて、一言。
Tilt your head here, and say one word.
オマルン、
Omaru-n,
好きだよ。
I like you.
わ、わ！
Wa, wa!
おい、オマルンお前冗談すんなや！
Hey, Omaru-n, don't joke around!
ごめんなさい、顔がさ、なんか、
Sorry, my face, somehow,
オマルンと雪花ラミィって似てるからさ、似てないよ！
Omaru-n and Yukihana Lamy look similar, so—they don't look similar!
いいでしょ、いいでしょ、いいでしょ、いいでしょ！
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
はい。
Yes.
お酒出るかな？
Will sake come out?
その魔法みたいな感じで出さんといて。
Don't bring it out like magic.
すごいよね、ポンって酒出てくるもんな。
It's amazing, sake just pops out.
いきます。お酒出るかどうか。
Here we go. Will sake come out or not?
おっ、あた、あた、あた、あた、すごい！
Oh, hit, hit, hit, hit, amazing!
はい。じゃあぜひシチュエーションをおお願いしてもよろしいですか？
Yes. So could you please give me a situation?
おおー。
Ooh.
喉越しね。
The feeling in the throat, huh.
え、飲んで？
Eh, drink?
あ、飲んでから？
Ah, after drinking?
あ、ラッパ、ラッパなんだね？
Ah, drinking straight from the bottle, huh?
グラス使わないんだ？
Not using a glass?
狙えないよ。日本酒はもっとどうやって飲むの？
You can't aim. How do you drink sake more?
えと、えと、おちょこがなくてさ、
Um, um, there's no small cup, so—
あ、BGM。
Ah, BGM.
あ、でもさ、両手で抱えてさ、なんかほら、こう？
Ah, but holding it with both hands like, look, like this?
あらあらあらあらあら！
Oh my goodness!
ラミィの日本酒。
Lamy's sake.
わあ！みんな美味しく飲んでね。
Wow! Everyone, drink up deliciously.
わあ！美味しい！
Wow! Delicious!
ちょっと海外の方いらっしゃいますか？おいおい！
Are there any people from overseas? Hey hey!
え、違う？
Eh, wrong?
ラミィ、あの、もうちょっと、あの、そこを片手で添えて、わかるか？それ両手、そうそうそう、そうそうそう、ちょっとカメラ近づいて。
Lamy, um, a bit more, support the bottom with one hand, you know? Both hands, right, right, get a bit closer to the camera.
あらあらあらあら！もっとカメラ近づいていいですよ！大丈夫ですよ、もっと恐がらず。
Oh my! You can get even closer to the camera! It's okay, don't be scared.
あ、そんな感じで。
Ah, something like that.
いいね、いいね。
Nice, nice.
どう？
How's that?
いいね、いいね。ラミィが作ったホロの酒。
Nice, nice. Holo sake made by Lamy.
わあ！2980円。
Wow! 2,980 yen.
あ、安い！
Ah, cheap!
買います！
I'll buy it!
ネネちゃん待って、ネネちゃん何で
Nene-chan wait, Nene-chan why did you—
ネネちゃん今日さ、日本人じゃなくて
Nene-chan today, instead of Japanese—
海外の方になるよね。
You'll become an overseas person.
はい！
Yes!
じゃあ、オマルンは終了！
Well then, Omaru-n is finished!
待ってごめん、最後に1個だけ、ねえ、やんで。
Wait sorry, just one last thing, hey, stop.
じゃあね、ちょっと、あ、見たい、見たい、
Well then, wait, ah, I want to see, I want to see,
ちょっと待って、ちょっと一旦ちょっと後ろ向いて。
hold on, wait, turn around for a second.
いいよ。
Sure.
後ろ向いて、振り返って、ヤンデレをするからちょっと、
Turn around, look back, and since I'm doing a yandere thing, wait,
な、セリフは？
hm, what about the lines?
セリフは、どうしようかな、
As for the lines, what should I do?
何がいいかな、みんな、
What would be good, everyone?
どんなヤンデレが好きかな、ラミィのは。
What kind of yandere do you like, Lamy's?
純粋な目で見てるよ、大福が。
Watching with pure eyes, Daifuku is.
本当だ！本当だ！本当だ！めっちゃ見てんじゃんこっち！
No way! No way! No way! You're staring right over here!
本当だ！
No way!
え、どうせ、なんて言う？
Eh, what would you say?
え、
Eh,
なんだろう、今日のお披露目ちゃんとすみずみまで見てよね、見てくれないと…
I wonder, you'll watch today's reveal right down to every detail, won't you? If you don't watch...
あー、なるほどね、いいよいいよ。
Ah, I see, okay okay.
はい、じゃあ、じゃあきゅんふりでお願いしまーす。
Yes, then, then kyun-free please.
３、２、１
3, 2, 1
ふっ。
Hmph.
みんな、今日ラミィのこと、すみずみまで見てくれないと、
Everyone, if you don't watch Lamy's every little detail today,
分かってるよね？
you understand, right?
はははは！
Hahaha!
ふいにー！ふい！ふい！
Fui! Fui! Fui!
ありがとうございます！はい、ありがとう！おまわりありがとう！
Thank you very much! Yes, thank you! Omawari thank you!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Good job!
え、それでは次はシシロン、お願いします！よーい、スタート！
Well then, next is Shishiron, please! Ready, start!
プロデュースか。
Producing, huh.
じゃあ、まあ、オマルンは全体的なさ、あのポーズしてとかいろいろ言ってたと思うから、私はちょっと、あの、やっぱりラミィちゃんのね、かわいい顔みたいな。
Well, Omarun talked about overall poses and stuff, so I thought, you know, I want to see Lamy's cute face.
なるほどね。そうそうそう。
I see. That's right, that's right.
ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょっとアップでアップでお願いします。
Um, a bit, a bit, close-up please.
あ、もう可愛い？あ、もう可愛い。もう優勝。
Ah, already cute? Ah, already cute. Already winning.
もう優勝優勝。可愛い。
Already winner, winner. Cute.
じゃあね、ちょっとさ、あの、じゃあまず基本の笑顔で、ちょっとあのシシロンってか、あ、シシロンプリ、
Well then, a bit, um, first with a basic smile, Shishiron-style, ah, Shishiron-puri,
シシロンプリ！
Shishiron-puri!
見てる！見てるの！
Watching! You're watching!
え、じゃあちょっと、ちょっと次、ちょっと、ちょっと怒った感じで、怒れるの？怒れるの？怒れるのね？
Eh, then next, with a slightly angry feel, can you get angry? Can you get angry? You can get angry, right?
アニメ的表現みたいなやつじゃん。わあ、浮気ばっかりしおって！
It's like an anime expression. Wow, running around cheating on me!
ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
じゃあ、ちょっと悲しい感じで、なんか、頼ってほしいな。なんかちょっと悲しい感じ、悲しい感じでお願いします。
Then, with a slightly sad vibe, like, I want you to rely on me. Something a bit sad, sad vibe please.
シシロン、なんで他の女の人ばっか行くの？
Shishiron, why do you only go to other women?
あ、すいません。これじゃ俺の嫁みたいじゃないか。
Ah, sorry. Doesn't this make it look like you're my bride?
悪いんだよ。
It's your fault.
すいません。許してください。
Sorry. Please forgive me.
ちゃんとシシラミちゃんやるんで許してください。
I'll properly do ShishiLamy so please forgive me.
言ったかな？聞いたかな？許してください。言ったかな？
Did I say it? Did you hear it? Please forgive me. Did I say it?
え、ほかなに、あるの？なんかこう、あ、じゃあ、
Eh, what else is there? Something like, ah, then,
ＰＭみたいな。
like PM.
ＰＭ？ＰＭできる？
PM? Can you do PM?
ＰＭ、ＰＭできる？
PM, can you do PM?
あ、ちょっと困り眉顔、な感じなんだね。あ、なるほどね。いいね、いいね、いいね。
Ah, a slightly troubled eyebrow look, that kind of vibe. Ah, I see. Nice, nice, nice.
え、でも、あ、どうしよう。プンプンポーズとか。
Eh, but, ah, what should I do? Like a pouting pose.
なんか、焦ってるのとかどう？焦ってる、焦ってる、焦ってる。
How about something like panicking? Panicking, panicking, panicking.
うわ、足ある！
Whoa, you have legs!
ちゃんと足ある！可愛い！
You actually have legs! Cute!
びっくりするけど。じゃあ、ちょっと困った顔で、なんかポーズしてほしいな。
It's surprising. Well then, with a troubled face, I want you to do some pose.
オマル先生、オマル先生。困った顔に似合うポーズってどんなのありますか？
Omarun-sensei, Omarun-sensei. What kind of poses suit a troubled face?
もうね、それは指をね、あの、人差し指をね、口に持ってきてね、
Well, you put your finger, um, your index finger to your mouth,
どうしようかな。で、首ぽてんぽてんっての可愛いです。
wondering what to do. And tilting your head is cute.
あ、いいじゃん！いいじゃん！も、もうちょっとちょっと上半身見せてほしいな。
Ah, that's good! That's good! Show a bit more of your upper body.
どうしようかな。どうしようかな。いいね。何ダンスしてんだよ。どうしようかな。
What should I do? What should I do? Nice. What dance are you doing? What should I do?
どうしようかな。
What should I do?
ちょっと違う。なんか違う。どうしようかなのポーズ。
That's a bit different. Something's different. The 'what should I do' pose.
あ、こうね。こうしようかな。こう。
Ah, like this. Let's do this. Like this.
いいね。いいね、いいね。それいいね。
Nice. Nice, nice. That's nice.
それ違う。可愛いけどそれはちょっと違う。違うか。ごめん。
That's different. It's cute, but that's a bit different. Is it different? Sorry.
うちのラミィがちょっとね、ラミィに求めすぎてる。なんか違う、違うなんか何かを求めて。
Our Lamy is a bit, demanding too much of Lamy. Something's different, looking for something else.
でもラミィは実際こんな、なんだろう、ぷよぷよ動いて可愛い動き、動く動く。
But Lamy actually moves around all squishy and cute, moving, moving.
押し付けがかなイメージもあるんだけど、この無邪気で可愛い感じが。わかるわかった。オマルわかったわかった。すいません。
There's also that somewhat pushy image, but this innocent, cute feeling. I get it, I get it. Omaru got it, got it. Sorry.
じゃあ、シシロ最後になにかありますか？
Well, Shishiro, is there anything at the end?
じゃあ、じゃあ全力笑顔で、ちょっとジャンプしてほしいな。あ、全力笑顔で。
Well then, with a full-force smile, I want you to jump a bit. Ah, full-force smile.
アイドルジャンプするよ
I'll do an idol jump!
アイドルステップも
And idol steps too.
練習したの
I practiced them!
いくよー。せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set!
じゃーーん！可愛い！
Ta-da! So cute!
どうですか？
How is it?
ありがとうございます！最高です！
Thank you so much! It's the best!
もう1回やってみます！
Let's do it one more time!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
じゃあ、最後に……
Now, lastly...
ねねちゃん、ねねプロデューサーさん
Nene-chan, Nene-producer-san...
任せたな！
I leave it to you!
ねねに任せとけ、みんな！
Leave it to Nene, everyone!
お願いします！じゃあ、ねねちゃんプロデューサーさん
Please! Okay, Nene-chan Producer-san,
よーい、スタート！
ready, start!
カメラさん、まず足元お願いします！太ももお願いします！
Camera-san, first my feet please! Thighs please!
やだ！早い早い早い早い！
No! Too fast, too fast, too fast!
食い込みやばくない？
Isn't it riding up a bit?
食い込み！
Riding up!
ラミィちゃん、ちょっと恥ずかしそうに足もじもじして。
Lamy-chan, look a little shy and squirm your feet.
もじもじ。
Squirm, squirm.
あららららら！もじもじ。
Oh my goodness! Squirm, squirm.
いいよ、いいよ。上上がってって。上上がって。
That's good, that's good. Move up. Move up.
もじもじ。いいよ、いいよ、いいよ。
Squirm, squirm. Good, good, good.
いい腰ですね！
Nice hips!
ああー！いいんですか？
Ahh! Is this okay?
そこアップいいんですか？
Is a close-up there okay?
そこってどこよ！
Where is "there"?!
えー、だめだねね！やっぱおっぱいがちょっと目に付いちゃうからさ。
Nene, no! My boobs kind of catch the eye too much.
下向いたらさ、やっぱ見えないのよ、床が。膝見えない、見えない。
If I look down, you can't see the floor. Can't see my knees.
あ、そうそう、そうそう。
Ah, right, right, right.
つま先とか見えないの？
You can't see my toes or anything?
あ、その前かがみいいな。前かがみお願いしていい？
Ah, leaning forward is good. Can I ask you to lean forward?
みんな（笑）。色々うるさいな。
Everyone (laughs). You guys are so noisy.
だめだよ！
No way!
いいぞ、いいぞ、いいぞ！ちょっとそのままだよ！
That's great, great, great! Stay just like that!
そのまま、そのままだよ。やだやだ、って横揺れして、まわって。
Stay right there. "No way, no way," shaking side to side, spinning.
やだやだ。
No way, no way.
おろおろ、おろおろね。素晴らしいじゃないですか！
Flustered, flustered. That's wonderful!
ラミィさん、ラミィさん、もしかしてなんですけど、上着、脱げちゃったりするんですか？
Lamy-san, Lamy-san, by any chance, can your jacket come off?
ではちょっといきますよ！
Well then, let's go!
じゃあ、ちょっといきますよ！
Now then, let's go!
せーの！
Ready, set!
ターン！ターン！すげるー！
Turn! Turn! Amazing!
素晴らしい！え、カメラマンさん！
Wonderful! Hey, cameraman-san!
脇！脇をお願いします！あ、脇見いてえな、脇見いてえな、脇見いてえな！
Armpits! Armpits please! Ah, I want to see armpits, want to see armpits!
は、初めて……！お、お、お、いや、すごい！
Th-this is the first... Wh-wh-whoa, amazing!
え、脇の、脇の筋やばい！
Hey, the muscle line of the armpit is crazy!
素晴らしい。ラミィさん、伸びしてほしいね、伸び。
Wonderful. Lamy-san, I want you to stretch, stretch.
あ、伸びね、伸びな。うーん、うーん、おおー！
Ah, stretch, stretch. Mmh, mmh, oooh!
え、私、ねねちゃんの番だけじゃなくて、下からも撮ってみたい！下からも撮ってみたい！
Hey, I want to take photos from below too, not just Nene-chan's turn!
いいね！いいね！
Sounds good! Sounds good!
ちょっと、もうちょい下、もっと下！
Wait, a bit more below, even lower!
足が、もっと
My legs, even more...
あ、おしり、おしり！
Ah, butt, butt!
カメラマンさん、おしり！
Cameraman-san, the butt!
何言ってるの本当ね、カメラマン。
What are you really saying, cameraman?
ねねちゃん、なかなかね、見られないからね。そうそうそうそう。
Nene-chan, you don't usually get to see it. That's right, right.
いいおしりですよ！
It's a nice butt!
え、ちょっとぷりぷりして、ぷりぷりして！
Hey, do a little wiggle, wiggle!
何、ぷりぷり？
What, wiggle?
止まりませんな！止まりませんな！おじさんだよ！
It won't stop! It won't stop! You sound like an old man!
あ、そのおしりからの脇のアングル最高だね！
Ah, that armpit angle from the butt is the best!
おしりからの脇、おしりからの、ああー！
Armpit from the butt, from the butt, ahh!
いいね！
Nice!
え、ラミィちゃんちょっと顔覗かせて、そっから。こっち見て。
Hey, Lamy-chan, peek your face out from there. Look this way.
あら！
Oh my!
いいの！
Is this okay?!
やくないよ！やくないよ！言い訳ないでしょ！
No it's not! No it's not! There's no excuse!
素晴らしい！言い訳ないでしょ！素晴らしい！
Wonderful! No excuse, right? Wonderful!
ねだぶー、ねだぶー。あ、ねだぶーだ！
Neda-boo, neda-boo. Ah, neda-boo!
ねだきんぶー！
Neda-kin-boo!
ねね、コメント見た感じさ、みんなめっちゃ喜んでくれてるよ、でも。
Nene, judging by the comments, everyone's super happy though.
えーっと、じゃあ、きりきり丸だ。
Um, well, Kirikiri-maru.
あ、よかったね。
Ah, that's good.
お耳の方とかもみたいの、お耳。
I want to see your ears and stuff too, your ears.
なかなかお耳の方。
Rarely see your ears.
その横顔とかさ、あ、横顔！
That profile and stuff, ah, profile!
いいなー！
Nice!
お、いいね！
Oh, nice!
え、なんその表情。え、美しい！
Eh, what is that expression? Eh, beautiful!
横顔、可愛いな、いいな。
Profile is so cute, nice.
横顔可愛い！可愛い、可愛い！
Profile is cute! Cute, cute!
え、そう、きゅってしてウィンクして、ポチッて。
Eh, like that, do a cute wink, and *click*.
とかね。あー、いいね！いいね！
Or something. Ah, nice! Nice!
え、素晴らしい！素晴らしい！なんて可愛いんだ、ラミィ！
Eh, wonderful! Wonderful! How cute are you, Lamy!
いやー、嫌がってるって！
No way, she's hating it!
嫌がってるって、待ってよ。
She's hating it, wait.
嫌がってるよね、ラミィちゃん。
She's hating it, right, Lamy-chan?
ちょっと変態さんが多いんで、着替えます。
There are a lot of perverts, so I'll change.
え、みんな気づいた、だって。
Eh, everyone noticed, you see.
帽子もないじゃん、帽子も。
There's no hat either, no hat.
あ、そう、帽子もね。
Ah, right, the hat too.
そうそうそう、帽子もね、そうだよね。
That's right, the hat too, yeah.
あ、帽子。つむじ！
Ah, hat. Cowlick!
ね、どういうあれなのよ。
Hey, what kind of deal is that?
待って、帽子着けてな！あ、帽子着けてな！
Wait, put the hat on! Ah, put the hat on!
つむじ、つむじみたい！つむじ！あ、残念。
Cowlick, I want to see the cowlick! Cowlick! Ah, too bad.
あーー！残念ーー！
Aahhh! Too bad—!
はい、じゃあ次。
Okay, then next.
ええと、最後。最後、何か1つあれば、やります。
Um, lastly. Lastly, if there's one thing left, I'll do it.
どうする？どうする？
What should we do? What should we do?
重要、重要だぞ、この最後。
Important, this last one is important.
そう、重要だよ、ラスト。
Yeah, it's important, the last one.
え、ちょっとじゃあコメントもみんなにも聞いてみよう。
Eh, then let's ask everyone in the comments too.
あ、立ちか座りか。
Ah, standing or sitting.
立ちか座りかまず、アンケート撮りたいな。
First, I want to take a poll on standing or sitting.
どれ、どれ、どれ、どれ？うんとね、待っててね。
Which, which, which, which? Um, wait a second.
どうする？
What should we do?
お前ら！
You guys!
何がいい？
What should we do?
体育座りだってよ。
Sitting with knees pulled up?
体育座り、あー、できるかな？
Knee-hug sit... I wonder if I can do that?
あ、座りが圧倒的に多いね。
Ah, sitting is overwhelmingly popular.
座りがいいんだ。
Sitting it is, then.
ちょっと危なさそうな場所に酒、酒置いとく？
Should I leave some sake in a somewhat dangerous spot?
あ、そうだね、酒置いておく。
Oh right, let's put some sake down.
どういうことだよ、それは。
What is that supposed to mean?!
どこに酒置いて…
Where should I put the sake...
本当に大福が移動してくれて…大福！
Daifuku actually moved for me... Daifuku!
守れ、大福守れ！
Protect me, protect Daifuku!
可愛い、守ってる！
So cute, he's protecting me!
ちょっとあの、なんだろう、こう、忍び寄る猫みたいな…
Wait, what is it, like creeping up like a cat...
忍び寄る猫だって！忍び寄る…
Creeping up like a cat! Creeping up...
ダメだな、その四つん這いの…あ！
No good, that all-fours... Ah!
えい！え、にゃんにゃん？
Take that! Eh, meow meow?
にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん、にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん！
Meow meow meow meow meow, meow meow meow meow meow!
おいおいおいおいおい！
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
どうする？買って帰るか、この、この猫ちゃん。
What should I do? Buy this kitty and take her home?
連れて帰ろう。
Let's take her home.
にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん！
Meow meow meow meow meow!
甘いセリフ？甘いセリフ？
Sweet lines? Sweet lines?
お願いします、お願いします。
Please, I'm begging you.
オッケー、行くよ。じゃあカウントダウンしてもいい？
Okay, here we go. Shall I do a countdown?
3、2、1、エッジ。
3, 2, 1, Edge.
ラミー猫、勝ってにゃん！にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん！
Lamy cat, win, meow! Meow meow meow meow meow!
はあ…はあ…
Ha... ha...
やっぱ審議が必要だわ、今のキャットヤバい。
We definitely need a review, that cat just now was dangerous.
あー、どうしよ…
Ah, what should I do...
どうしよ…え、どういうこと？ねえプロデューサーさん。
What should I do... Eh, what do you mean? Hey, Mr. Producer.
プロデューサーさん、ありがとうございます！
Producer-san, thank you very much!
ええ、物足りない、物足りない。
Eh, not enough, not enough.
おしまい！
That's it!
ということで、今回はここでね、視聴者の皆さんにアンケートを撮りたいと思います。
So, this time, I'd like to take a poll from all the viewers here.
コメントで今から、よかったと思うプロデューサーさんの名前を…
In the comments, starting now, please write the name of the producer you think was the best...
プルカとか、ボタン、ねね。え、これはプルカがカタカナでねねがひらがな、ボタンがひらがな…
Like Pulka, Botan, Nene. Pulka in katakana, Nene in hiragana, Botan in hiragana...
え、一人1回、1回コメントに打ってください。
Please type it in the comments once per person.
で、自分でボタンて書こ。
And I'll write Botan for myself.
ちゃんとスタートって言ってからストップって言うまで待ってください。
Please wait until I say "Start" and then "Stop".
はいはい、分かった分かった。
Got it, got it.
それでは、もう準備万端。風景スタート！
Well then, we're all set. Landscape start!
ねね、ねね、みんなねねだよね。
Nene, Nene, everyone is Nene, right?
またんだね、じゃあ。やっぱこれはねねだよ。
It's Nene again, then. As expected, it's Nene.
ねね、ねらみ、ほら、クルッて回って。クルッ？クルッ。
Nene, Nerami, look, spin around. Spin? Spin.
はあ…ただを見たいだけじゃねえかよ。
Ha... You just want to look at me, don't you?
見たいだけ見たらさ、いや、でもだって、もうずっと見てたし。あ、確かにな。
Once you've seen all you want... well, but you've been watching the whole time. Ah, true.
えと、ちなみに、あの、ねねとか、できればその名前だけでお願いします。
By the way, uh, Nene, etc., if possible, please just use the name.
あ、寄れる、寄れるだけ。あ、鼻埋めねが綺麗ね。
Ah, getting close, just getting close. Ah, Nene burying her nose is pretty.
あれ？もしや…中してる？
Huh? Could it be... kissing?
してないよ！
I am NOT!
どういうことよ！
What's that supposed to mean!
え、10秒、あと集計10秒です。
Eh, 10 seconds, 10 more seconds for tallying.
10、9、8、
10, 9, 8,
ねねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、ねね、1！
Nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, nene, 1!
ラミーがスタートするよ、もう。幸福でごめんなさいね。
Lamy is going to start now. Sorry for being happy.
何言ってんのもう！
What are you even saying!
えと、ということで、えっと、集計終了しましたかね。
So, um, I guess the tallying has ended.
発表できるのかな？ドキドキ！
Can we announce it? I'm so nervous!
名誉プロデューサーになるねねが、どうやら中らしいです。
It seems Nene, who will become the honorary producer, is currently tallying.
じゃあラミーね、すごいのもあったのね。ちゃんと集計してるんだ。
Well then, Lamy, there were some amazing ones too. You're properly tallying them.
そうなんです、これね、ちょっと新しい集計システムが入りまして。
That's right, a new tallying system was introduced for this.
ラミーのアイドルステップを見て。上手、上手。
Look at Lamy's idol step. Good, good.
ね、どう？ね、どう？え、可愛い！
Hey, how is it? Hey, how is it? Eh, so cute!
待って待って、違うとこ行っちゃうな。何言ってるの、おじさん！
Wait, wait, it's going somewhere different. What are you saying, mister!
ねねおじさん、やめなよ。今日すごいよ、ねねちゃん。
Nene-ojisan, stop it. Today is amazing, Nene-chan.
はい、ということで、集計の準備ができたそうなので、結果を見ていきたいと思います。
All right, so it looks like the tallying preparations are complete, so let's take a look at the results.
それでは、結果はこちら！どうぞ！
Well then, here are the results! Ta-da!
え、待って待って！みんな1位だなぁ！
Eh, wait wait! Everyone is #1!
結果は、ねねすら118ポイント、おまれん92...
The results are: Nenesura 118 points, Omaren 92...
ポイント
Points!
ネネおじさんが860ポイントということですね！
Nene-ojisan got 860 points, which means...
おじさん！おじさんたち！
Ojisan! You guys are ojisan!
ネネおじさんの優勝です！
Nene-ojisan is the winner!
やったー！
Yay!
さすが！ねぇ、おじさんたち！
As expected! Hey, you guys!
やった！
Yay!
なんか、あれだね。なんかちょっと、う、ラミもこれはどうかと思います。
Well, you know... I think Lamy herself has mixed feelings about this.
最高だね、みんな！
You guys are the best!
本当、お前ら好きだな。おじさんたちも好きだけどな。
Seriously, I love you guys. Well, I like you guys too!
え、ということでね、3人ともどうもありがとう！
So anyway, thank you all three so much!
おじさん！ありがとう！
Ojisan! Thank you!
あれ、出できた、出できた、やっと帰ってきた。
Oh, they're back, they're back, they finally returned.
あ、すいませーん、なんか出ちゃってすいませーん。邪魔しちゃってすいませーん。
Ah, sorry, sorry for appearing out of nowhere. Sorry for interrupting!
いや、ごきげんが重なり合ってさらに最高になるということで。
Well, good vibes overlapping makes it even better.
そうだね。これからもプロデューサーして下さい。
That's right. Please continue being our producers.
え、ちょっと、お、お胸のどこいけないの、それで。
Wait, why can't you look at my chest like that?
え、何？どういうこと？
Eh, what? What do you mean?
なんて？え、ちょっと？
What? Wait?
あ、何してんだ、お姉ちゃん！
Ah, what are you doing, big sis!
はい、ありがとう！ありがとう！みんな、またね、ありがとう！お邪魔しました！
Yes, thank you! Thank you! See you guys later, thank you! Sorry for interrupting!
え、ということでね、ごきげん…みんな、ありがとう！
So anyway... good vibes... thank you everyone!
いや、なんかすごくこう、みんなの、いろんなことが分かったポーズ、希望だったなと思います。
Well, I feel like this was a pose where we really got to understand everyone's various sides.
え、ということで、えっと、ここからは、今ねちょっと準備してるんで、え、ちょっとね、じゃあラミ準備してくるんで、このままお待ちくださーい！ばいばーい！
And with that, um, from here on... I'm getting ready right now, so um, Lamy's gonna go get ready, please wait right here! Bye-bye!
皆さんどうも、ナレーションの雪花ラミィです。
Hello everyone, I'm your narrator, Yukihana Lamy.
今回はモーニングルーティンに続いて、ナイトルーティンにも挑戦していきたいと思います。
Following my morning routine, today I'd like to try out my night routine.
外から帰ってきたらまずははお着替えです。お部屋では少しでも動きやすい格好で過ごしたいんですよね。
As soon as I get back home, the first thing I do is change clothes. I like to wear something comfortable to move around in while in my room.
えっと、その次、お、あとこれは、これは、えっと、サービス、
Um, next... oh, and this, this is, um, fan service?
これちょっとね、あのラミいつの間にか撮られてたんだか分からないんですが、これは運営さん的にオッケーなのでしょうか？え、どういうことなのか？
I'm not even sure when Lamy ended up being filmed like this, but is management really okay with this? What's going on here?
そしてネルーシェの練習をします。配信で演奏する前には必ず練習をしています。ちょっと聞いてみましょう。
Next, I practice playing the Neluce. I always practice before performing on stream. Let's take a listen.
え、その後はお料理をします。夕飯はけっこうしっかり食べることが多いですね。
Afterwards, I cook dinner. I usually make sure to have a hearty dinner.
よく食べるのは鶏肉。安くてボリュームもある鶏胸肉がすごく好きで、生姜焼きなんかも鶏胸肉で作ったりしています。
What I eat often is chicken. I really love chicken breast because it's cheap and filling, so I even make ginger pork-style chicken breast with it.
そしてそのあとにはやっぱり晩酌です！今みたいな寒い時期にはおでんが最高ですよね。
And after that, of course, comes evening drinks! Oden is simply the best during cold seasons like this.
これ日本酒ともばっちりの相性でもたまりません。これだけ割りにしても美味しいので、1石2鳥、3鳥、4鳥、5鳥ですね。あ、もうなくなったって怒ってますね、これ。
It goes so wonderfully with Japanese sake that it's irresistible. It's delicious no matter what you pair it with, so that's like killing five birds with one stone. Ah, it's already gone, you're getting mad at me aren't you?
あー！
Ah!
はあ どういう構造をしているのか おちょこ
Ah, I wonder what kind of structure this ochoko has...
あ すごい飲みますね
Ah, she drinks a lot.
ああ だめです 瓶から直接飲んだらだめです
Ah, no good. Drinking straight from the bottle is no good.
あ 今回ね あの 特別 に ああ だめですね それもだめですね
Ah, this time, specially... Ah, no good, that's no good either.
今回特別にま 演出ということなんで いつもはこうじゃないです
This time it's specially staged, so it's not usually like this.
本当です 本当です
Really, really!
まだ まだ執着してますね
Still... still obsessed, huh.
すごい執着心
Such an obsession.
そして 一通り飲んだあとは就寝です
And after drinking her fill, it's bedtime.
皆様はどのような夜を過ごされていますでしょうか
How are all of you spending your night?
おやすみなさい 雪花ラミィでした
Good night. This was Yukihana Lamy.
えということ で 皆さんにねモーニングルーティンナイトルーティン見ていただきましたがどうだったでしょうか
So, you just watched my morning and night routines, how was it?
えここでね ちょっとね あの ま 今回 ラミィね3Dに慣れたということで
Um, so here, um, well, this time, since Lamy got used to 3D...
ま ちょっとね すごくラミィの中で 本当にこのなんていうのかな
Well, um, deep inside Lamy, I really... how should I say this...
去年 のちょうど 今日 1年前 にね この ライブを見て
...watching this live exactly one year ago today...
この ライブの先輩方がすごくこのキラキラアイドルしている姿を見て いつかラミィもそこに立ちたいと 思っておりました
...seeing how sparkling and idol-like the seniors were in this live, I always thought I wanted to stand there someday.
それが 今日今 ここにいられることはすごく何というか 感慨深いというか 奇跡のような 今だにちょっと信じられない気持ちでは あります
That today, right now, being able to be here is, how should I put it, so deeply moving, like a miracle, and part of me still can't quite believe it.
ええ ラミィはね 歌も下手だし ダンスもできないし 運動も苦手なんだけれども
Um, Lamy's bad at singing, can't dance, and isn't good at sports either, but...
ま でもね 先輩方がキラキラ輝いていた あの場所にいつか行けるように
Well, but... so that I can someday reach that place where my seniors shone brightly,
これからも 活動も歌もダンスも頑張っていけたらな と 思っています
I hope to keep doing my best in my activities, singing, and dancing from now on.
ま そういうね 少しずつの成長ですが 皆さんに これからも ちょっとずつそういうラミィを 見ていただけると嬉しいです
Well, it's a slow, step-by-step growth, but I'd be happy if you continue to watch Lamy grow little by little.
え ということで え ちょっと しみじみしてしまったところで
Um, with that said, having gotten a bit sentimental here,
ここからは ラミィが この アイドルだという 第1歩 を 皆さんに 見ていただけたら 嬉しいな と 思います
from here on, I'd be happy if everyone could watch Lamy take her first step as an idol.
それでは 皆さん 心の準備は いいですか！ いいよ！ よし
Well then, everyone, is your heart ready?! Ready! Alright.
それでは 行きまーす よー じゃーん！
Well then, let's go! Ready, ta-da!
可愛くね とびきりの愛を 届け
Deliver your cutest, extraordinary love!
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えてて
If you don't mind, please remember even just my name!
レッスン開始！
Lesson start!
意気込むけれど
I'm enthusiastic, but
歌って 踊って ヘトヘト
singing and dancing leaves me exhausted,
ヘッドヘッド比較される事もあるけれど
and sometimes I get compared to others,
私は私で ありたい
but I want to be myself.
本気出さないと響かないんだ
If I don't give it my all, it won't resonate.
ファンの心を掴みたいんだ
I want to capture the fans' hearts,
だからスタート全開飛ばしますよ
so starting full throttle, I'll speed ahead!
可愛くね とびきりの愛を 届け！
Deliver your cutest, extraordinary love!
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えていて下さい
If you don't mind, please remember even just my name!
あざとくね とびきりの笑顔で！
With a cunningly cute, extraordinary smile!
宜しければ“推し”にしちゃってくれませんか？
Won't you make me your oshi?
なんてねっ！ちょっぴりマジなのは期待していいですか？
Just kidding! Can I expect you to be a little serious?
ちょっぴりマジなの期待していい
Can I expect you to be serious?
可愛くね とびきりの愛を届け！
Cute, delivering my very best love!
宜しければ名前だけでも覚えてっ て下さい
If you don't mind, please at least remember my name!
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
レッスン開始！ 気合入る だけど
Lessons start! I'm pumped, but...
歌って 踊って ヘトヘト
singing and dancing leaves me exhausted.
比較される 事もある けど
Sometimes I get compared to others,
私は私で ありたい
but I just want to be myself.
本気出さなきゃ 響かないんだ
If I don't give it my all, it won't resonate,
ファンの心 を掴みたいんだ
and I want to capture my fans' hearts.
だからスタート全開 飛ばしますよ
So I'll start running full throttle!
（You're my angel !!）
(You're my angel!!)
可愛くね とびきりの愛を届け！
Cute, delivering my very best love!
宜しければ名前だけでも覚えてっ て下さい
If you don't mind, please at least remember my name!
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
あざとくね とびきりのスマイルで！
Cunningly, with a dazzling smile!
宜しければ "推し"にしちゃってくれませんか？
Won't you make me your favorite?
なんてねっ！ 笑
Just kidding! Haha.
ちょっぴりマジな の期待していいですか？
Can I hope you're being a little serious?
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
人生変えるそんな 一日
A single day that changes my life,
憧れ夢見た ステージ
the stage I've always dreamed of.
オシャレ？ 流行り？ 追いかけなくて
Chic? Trendy? I won't chase after those;
言い訳 弱音も出しちゃうよ
I end up making excuses and whining too.
向いてないかな？
Am I not cut out for this?
愛想悪いしこんなアイドル他にいないし
I'm unfriendly and unlike any other idol,
でもね絶対絶対見返すんだ
but I will definitely, absolutely prove them wrong!
（You're my angel !!）
(You're my angel!!)
愛してね "日本一"夢見てる
Love me, I'm dreaming of being #1 in Japan!
宜しければ合いの手一つ入れてやって下さい
If you don't mind, throw in a call-and-response for me!
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
手を上げて視線独り占めして！
Raise your hands and hog all my attention!
宜しければ愛を恵んでくれませんか？
If you don't mind, won't you bestow your love on me?
なんてねっ！ 笑
Just kidding! Haha.
絶対後悔させませんよ？マジでね！！
I definitely won't let you regret it! Seriously!!
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
今もステージは胸がギュッと熱くなる
Even now, my chest aches and grows warm on stage,
揺れる景色焼き付けて歌う声に愛を込める
burning the swaying scenery into my eyes, pouring love into my singing voice.
響く歓声気持ち高鳴る
Resonating cheers make my heart race,
これは証明私ここだよ
this is proof that I am right here!
いくよ！
Here I go!
絶対絶対声出してね？
Make sure you shout out loud, okay?
（You're my angel !!）
(You're my angel!!)
可愛くね とびきりの愛を届け！
Cute, delivering my very best love!
宜しければ名前だけでも覚えてっ て下さい
If you don't mind, please at least remember my name!
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
あざとくね とびきりのスマイルで！
Cunningly, with a dazzling smile!
宜しければ "推し"にしちゃってくれませんか？
Won't you make me your favorite?
なんてねっ！ 笑
Just kidding! Haha.
（You're my angel !!）
(You're my angel!!)
ちょっぴりマジな の期待していいですか？
Can I hope you're being a little serious?
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
飛び切りの愛を届け
Delivering my absolute best love,
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えててください
if you don't mind, please remember just my name.
あざとくね 飛び切りのスマイルで
Cunningly, with a dazzling smile,
よろしければ推しにしちゃってくれませんか
won't you make me your favorite?
なんてねっ！
Just kidding!
ちょっぴりマジなの期待していいですか
Can I hope you're being a little serious?
（ハイ！）
(Yes!)
はあ〜！
Haah!
みんな！ありがとうございました！
Everyone! Thank you so much!
それでは ここでお知らせがあります！
Now, I have an announcement to make!
じゃん！雪花ラミィ 3D化記念グッズ！
Ta-da! Yukihana Lamy's 3D commemorative merchandise!
1月24日販売開始！
On sale starting January 24th!
記念グッズ全2種あります！
There are 2 types of commemorative goods in total!
1個目は、3Dアクリルスタンド！
The first one is a 3D acrylic stand!
出ますでしょうか？
Can we put it on screen?
じゃん！
Ta-da!
こちら…
Here is...
あ、違う！あ、違う、こちらです！
Ah, wait! No, no, it's this one!
アクリルスタンドになっております。こちら、え、縦の高さが145mmとなっております！
It's an acrylic stand. This one has a height of 145mm!
そしてもう一つがこちら！
And the other one is right here!
じゃん！ 「BARゆきはな」特製アイスキューブ！
Ta-da! "BAR Yukihana" special ice cubes!
こちらが、え、25mm×25mm×25mmの、正方形のアイスキューブとなっております。
These are square ice cubes measuring 25mm x 25mm x 25mm.
こちらが飲み物をあの、冷やすのに、保冷するのに使うものになっていてステンレス製なので何度でも使えます。
These are used for chilling drinks and keeping them cold. Since they're made of stainless steel, you can use them over and over again.
あの、冷蔵庫でね冷やして飲み物入れておくと、あの、味が薄まらないで飲めるっていう、あの、ウイスキーとか梅酒とか、お酒に（笑）、お酒じゃなくてもいいけど、お酒のおトモに使っていただけるといいかもしれません！
If you chill them in the fridge and put them in your drink, you can enjoy it without the flavor getting diluted—whether it's whiskey, plum wine, or alcohol (laughs)—well, it doesn't have to be alcohol, but they might be great to use with drinks!
こちらね、えっと、今日の21時、9時にカートが開きますので皆さんよかったらお迎えしてください！
These will go on sale tonight at 21:00 (9 PM), so please pick them up if you'd like!
え、ということでね、えっと…ここまでのないようかやりましたけれども…（笑）、え、最後に…
So, um... we've gone through all the details so far... (laughs), um, lastly...
1曲
One song,
聞いていただければと思います
I hope you'll listen to it.
それでは聞いてください。キラメキライダー！
Now then, please listen. Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高の時間 最高の仲間と キラメキにのって
With the best time, the best friends, riding on the sparkles
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
声が震えていた
When our voices were trembling?
あの日から続く未来は みんなとつかんだ今日だよ
The future since that day is today we grasped together with everyone
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
Accelerating our hearts more and more and more
行くよどこまでも
Going anywhere
準備はOK?
Are you ready?
ひらけ夢の扉を!
Open the door of dreams!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Because you found me here
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌を
I came to see you, let's sing together
終わらないメロディ キラメキにのって
Riding on the endless melody and sparkles
届いてるかな 私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
昨日の涙を悔しくって
Regretting yesterday's tears
みんなで泣き笑ったね ギュッとギュッとギュッとギュッと 全て抱きしめて
We cried and laughed together, hugging everything tight
行こうどこまでも
Going anywhere
準備はOK?
Are you ready?
進め 希望の道も!
Press forward on the path of hope!
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいんだ
I want to play my favorite feelings colorfully
最後の場所 最高の仲間と ここにいるよ
In the final place with the best friends, I am here
幻なんかじゃない 君の心が
It's no illusion, your heart
幸せに染まるように 重ねてくハーモニー キラメキにのって
So that it is dyed in happiness, piling up harmonies, riding on the sparkles
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな そんな願いが わがままでもいいでしょ
I want to keep singing and dancing, even if such a wish is selfish
だって楽しいすぎて止まらない 輝くステージで もっともっともっと
Because it's too fun to stop, on the shining stage, more and more!
ずっとずっと
On and on!
嬉しい楽しい、愛しいだけじゃ語れない
You can't describe it with just happy, fun, and lovely
今も今もあるけど 悩みはあるけど
Even now, though there are worries, I am here
私ここにいるよ
I am here
君と同じ世界を見つめて 見つめて キラメキにのって
Gazing at the same world as you, riding on the sparkles
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高の時間 最高の仲間と キラメキにのって
With the best time, the best friends, riding on the sparkles
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Because you found me here
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came to see you
みんなで歌を 終わらないメロディ
Singing together with everyone, an endless melody
キラメキにのって キラメキまとって
Riding on the sparkles, wearing the sparkles
みんな、あ、ありがとう！
Everyone, ah, thank you!
みんな、ありがとう！
Everyone, thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
雪花ラミィ 3D お披露目
[Yukihana Lamy 3D Debut]